<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BryanCruz</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Freelancer</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:58:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Descripción (ES)</title>
		<link>/descripcion/</link>
					<comments>/descripcion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Cruz Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hola, Soy Bryan Santiago Cruz Angel, a continuación encontrarás una breve descripcion de mi Perfil: Profesional de Ingeniería Biomédica de la Escuela Colombiana de Ingeniería Julio Garavito en convenio con la Universidad delRosario. Con interés en el desarrollo de software, mantenimiento de equipos médicos y Gestión hospitalaria. Cuento con experienciaen atención al cliente y proyectos [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hola, Soy <strong>Bryan Santiago Cruz Angel</strong>, a continuación encontrarás una breve descripcion de mi Perfil:</p>



<p class="has-drop-cap">Profesional de Ingeniería Biomédica de la Escuela Colombiana de Ingeniería Julio Garavito en convenio con la Universidad del<br>Rosario. Con interés en el desarrollo de software, mantenimiento de equipos médicos y Gestión hospitalaria. Cuento con experiencia<br>en atención al cliente y proyectos de investigación con inteligencia artificial. Conocimientos en normativa de equipos médicos,<br>lenguajes de programación como CSS3, HTML5, JS, Python, entre otros. Aptitud en el desarrollo de sistemas informáticos para<br>centros de salud y trabajo en equipo</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/descripcion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Description (EN)</title>
		<link>/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Cruz Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 16:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hello, I am Bryan Santiago Cruz Angel, below you will find a brief description of my Profile: Biomedical Engineering Professional from the Julio Garavito Colombian School of Engineering in agreement with the Universidad delRosary beads. Interested in software development, medical equipment maintenance, and hospital management. I have experiencein customer service and research projects with artificial [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hello, I am <strong>Bryan Santiago Cruz Angel</strong>, below you will find a brief description of my Profile:</p>



<p>Biomedical Engineering Professional from the Julio Garavito Colombian School of Engineering in agreement with the Universidad del<br>Rosary beads. Interested in software development, medical equipment maintenance, and hospital management. I have experience<br>in customer service and research projects with artificial intelligence. Knowledge of medical equipment regulations,<br>programming languages such as CSS3, HTML5, JS, Python, among others. Aptitude in the development of computer systems for<br>health centers and teamwork.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
